sophomore song, but y'all are open. So,
>> Oh, good. Um, hey, congratulations. What
What does this uh mean to you? And did
you have any idea that the Saints were a
team that you could end up with?
>> Yeah, this means everything, man. I'm
ready to give, you know, this whole this
organization my all. Um, I'm just super
excited. Um, talked to Saints a little
bit, um, both at the combine and and,
uh, was really, you know, happy with my
experience with them and and, uh, the
coaching staff. So, I'm super excited.
>> Bryce, you obviously already have a
brother who's been through the process.
Don't let him tell you about it.
>> Uh, yeah. Honestly, about this whole
process, um, you know, he just told me
to be myself. You know, he knows I'm a
hard worker, a good person, a genuine
dude. Um, so he just, you know, let me
let me know that God's got God's got
going to handle the rest. And, you know,
I just got to just got to do me.
>> What is it about the uh North Dakota
State program that produces so many of
you NFL guys?
Yeah, you know, we've been in FCS all
these years, but um I really don't think
you compare us to, you know, average FCS
program. Um we hold ourselves to a
really high standard. Uh the standard is
a national championship. You know, I
don't care what level that is. That
that's a hard thing to do. So, um like I
said, we hold ourselves to a really hard
standard and we pride ourselves on, you
know, doing the doing doing the hard
work and all the little things um you
know, to to to achieve a championship.
Hey guys, hang on one second. Bryce, is
your screen rotation unlock?
Yes, there we go.
>> Let's just try to rotate it again real
quick before we keep going. Sorry, guys.
>> Okay,
>> Bryce, couple of questions. Uh, do you
know do you know any players on the
Saints team? And are you familiar with
the city of New Orleans? Have you been
here?
>> Uh, never been to to the city? No. Um,
but been a big fan fan of the receiving
room, Chris especially, and all the
things he has done. Um, so I'm super
excited to learn from him and um, just
compete every day.
>> Bryce, how much of a influence did your
brother have on you? What was it like
growing up together?
>> Yeah, a ton. A ton. That's my best
friend. That's my guy. You know, he's
he's got me for life and I got him the
same way. Um, you know, obviously he's
been in in this industry for a while, so
I've been able to learn a lot um, both
the football side and the business side
of things. So, um, he's he's played a
very large part in my journey. What did
it mean to you to run a 4-3 at the
combine? And um were you expecting to
run that?
>> Yes, sir. Yes, sir. I was expecting to
run um low 43s. Um I was just super
happy with the way uh the combine
performance turned out. Uh I pride
myself on hard work, like I said
earlier. So, just that whole combine
prep uh uh time um and just grind it.
So, I was happy with the results. what
strengths uh what do you feel like are
your strengths as a receiver and and
what areas would you like to work on?
>> Yeah, for sure. I think um
receiver-wise, I think I have elite ball
skills. You know, when the ball's in the
air, it's mine or nobodyies. That's
something I always pride myself on. Um I
think I play the game at a really fast
pace. Um I think I learn really quick. I
can read defenses, things like that. Um,
I think, you know, the receiver position
is a super technical position, so I
think I can get better at the technical
aspects of that. Um, I'm super excited
to learn from those guys and and coach
and um, just to improve, uh, overall.
>> How are you as a blocker?
>> Oh, great. We we don't play if you can't
block. So, that that that that was that
was my role for a while.
>> Um, Saints been doing a lot of work on
the offensive side of the ball
throughout this draft class. just, you
know, what does it what does it say to
you that they've included you as a part
of the, you know, clear um endeavor of
adding more playmakers to this offense?
>> Yeah, means everything. Uh, you know,
all it takes is one and the fact that
these guys believe in me and this
coaching staff believes in me. I'm ready
to earn earn that trust and earn that
belief honestly with both the coaching
staff and my teammates as well. Um, like
I said, you know, the goal is
championships and, you know, that's
that's what I'm bringing uh, you know,
my desire to win championships to this
organization.
You know, there aren't there aren't a
lot of domes in college, but, you know,
the Fargo Dome is is kind of unique. Um,
does does that help at all just being
familiar with the dome setting? You come
you're playing in the Superdome now?
>> Yeah, I think for sure. I mean, I've
played in all sorts of stadiums
obviously, but um yeah, I think playing
in a dome definitely has its benefits,
you know, to correlating to playing in
another dome for sure. Just the lighting
and things like that. So,
>> are you excited to make the leap from
Minnesota and North Dakota to a warmer
climate? [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah. No doubt. You know,
throughout this draft process, you know,
people were asking me where you want to
go and I I just remember saying, you
know, somewhere warm wouldn't be too
bad. So warm wouldn't be too bad. So the
just is a added benefit, you know, to to
my situation.
>> You got warm for sure. I can promise
you. [laughter and clears throat]
>> Anything else for Bryce?
>> Thanks.
>> Congrats, Bryce.
>> All right, guys.
>> Awesome. Thank you, guys. brace.